1
00:00:04,616 --> 00:00:05,878
What am l sitting on?

2
00:00:06,385 --> 00:00:07,852
Top of the world?

3
00:00:08,186 --> 00:00:09,949
Dock of the bay?

4
00:00:10,989 --> 00:00:12,047
l'm out.

5
00:00:14,126 --> 00:00:15,150
Oh, undies!

6
00:00:19,331 --> 00:00:21,162
Whose are they?

7
00:00:21,400 --> 00:00:23,527
-Whose are they?
-Not mine.

8
00:00:23,802 --> 00:00:25,463
Joey's!
Got to be Joey's.

9
00:00:30,309 --> 00:00:31,298
They're mine.

10
00:00:31,577 --> 00:00:34,375
See, Joey's.
They're Joe-Joe-Joey's.

11
00:00:35,180 --> 00:00:36,477
Why are they here?

12
00:00:37,149 --> 00:00:38,741
l don't know.

13
00:00:41,053 --> 00:00:42,486
l'm Joey.

14
00:00:43,522 --> 00:00:44,580
l'm disgusting.

15
00:00:44,823 --> 00:00:47,553
l take my underwear off
in other people's homes.

16
00:00:49,428 --> 00:00:52,556
Get them out of here.
What's wrong with you?

17
00:00:56,168 --> 00:00:58,159
-Take them!
-l got them.

18
00:00:58,770 --> 00:01:01,364
You can touch them.
They're yours.

19
00:01:06,678 --> 00:01:08,236
Chandler? A word?

20
00:01:16,688 --> 00:01:20,954
l'm tired of covering for you two.
This has got to stop.

21
00:01:22,761 --> 00:01:24,922
Tighty-whiteys?
What are you, 8?

22
00:01:26,465 --> 00:01:28,524
Thank you, Joey, so much.

23
00:01:28,800 --> 00:01:30,267
You're not welcome, okay?

24
00:01:30,802 --> 00:01:34,363
Look, l hate this.
You guys keep embarrassing me.

25
00:01:34,606 --> 00:01:38,133
Yesterday, Rachel found
your razor in our bathroom.

26
00:01:38,377 --> 00:01:42,473
l said it was mine, and that
l was playing a woman in a play.

27
00:01:44,116 --> 00:01:46,482
Then one thing led
to another, and....

28
00:01:51,957 --> 00:01:54,983
And around the ankles,
that is a tough spot.

29
00:01:55,227 --> 00:01:56,922
lt was.
All right, listen--

30
00:01:57,162 --> 00:01:59,562
All this lying has been
hard on us too.

31
00:01:59,798 --> 00:02:02,392
Yeah, l bet all the sex
makes it easier.

32
00:02:04,236 --> 00:02:05,760
Yeah, actually.

33
00:02:06,238 --> 00:02:09,537
Meanwhile, l get Rachel shoving your
underwear in my face...

34
00:02:09,708 --> 00:02:13,007
...and asking when she can
come see me star in <i>Ugly Woman.</i>

35
00:02:14,479 --> 00:02:15,844
We'll be more careful.

36
00:02:16,081 --> 00:02:20,017
We don't want them to know
because it's going really well.

37
00:02:20,752 --> 00:02:23,812
And maybe it's going well
because it's a secret.

38
00:02:24,089 --> 00:02:27,581
lt sounds weird,
but we're so bad at relationships.

39
00:02:27,993 --> 00:02:29,858
-We are. Help us!
-Help!

40
00:02:31,797 --> 00:02:35,494
All right.
But you do it with me once.

41
00:02:39,738 --> 00:02:41,865
-Joey!
-Didn't think so.

42
00:02:44,776 --> 00:02:46,641
The One With Ross' Sandwich

43
00:03:32,390 --> 00:03:35,450
-Can we please just drop this?
-But l don't get it.

44
00:03:35,627 --> 00:03:39,495
Does anybody else just take off
their underwear when they're hot?

45
00:03:43,969 --> 00:03:45,027
What are you reading?

46
00:03:45,771 --> 00:03:46,760
<i>Wuthering Heights.</i>

47
00:03:46,972 --> 00:03:51,033
l have to finish it by tomorrow
for my literature class.

48
00:03:51,276 --> 00:03:53,540
You're taking a class?
That's so cool.

49
00:03:53,912 --> 00:03:56,881
l really liked
that Lamaze class l took.

50
00:03:57,149 --> 00:04:00,812
l thought this time l'd go
for something more intellectual...

51
00:04:01,119 --> 00:04:03,417
...with a less painful final exam.

52
00:04:04,790 --> 00:04:06,314
That sounds like fun.

53
00:04:06,658 --> 00:04:08,819
Oh, you should come with me!

54
00:04:09,060 --> 00:04:11,221
Then l'll have someone to sit with.

55
00:04:13,565 --> 00:04:15,294
Do you have time to read it?

56
00:04:15,500 --> 00:04:16,489
l read it in school.

57
00:04:16,768 --> 00:04:20,727
This is going to be so much fun!
l have to finish.

58
00:04:23,074 --> 00:04:25,474
But what time does the class start?

59
00:04:32,050 --> 00:04:33,039
What's wrong, buddy?

60
00:04:33,251 --> 00:04:35,651
Someone at work ate my sandwich.

61
00:04:37,656 --> 00:04:39,681
What did the police say?

62
00:04:40,692 --> 00:04:43,661
My Thanksgiving leftover sandwich.

63
00:04:43,895 --> 00:04:45,760
l can't believe someone ate it.

64
00:04:45,997 --> 00:04:47,225
lt's just a sandwich.

65
00:04:47,499 --> 00:04:49,057
Just a sandwich?

66
00:04:49,334 --> 00:04:51,234
l am 30 years old, okay?

67
00:04:51,503 --> 00:04:53,835
l'll be divorced twice and
l got evicted.

68
00:04:54,072 --> 00:04:57,269
That sandwich was
the only good thing in my life!

69
00:04:57,509 --> 00:05:01,343
Someone ate the only good thing
going on in my life!

70
00:05:03,348 --> 00:05:04,610
That's a nice sweater vest.

71
00:05:06,952 --> 00:05:09,216
l have enough
for one more sandwich.

72
00:05:09,454 --> 00:05:12,014
l was going to eat it myself, but....

73
00:05:13,458 --> 00:05:17,155
Mon, that would be incredible.
Thank you so much.

74
00:05:17,629 --> 00:05:20,359
l still can't believe
someone ate it!

75
00:05:22,534 --> 00:05:24,798
Look, l left a note and everything.

76
00:05:26,004 --> 00:05:27,403
''Knock-knock.''
''Who's there?''

77
00:05:27,672 --> 00:05:29,469
''Ross Geller's lunch.''

78
00:05:30,375 --> 00:05:32,400
''Ross Geller's lunch, who?''

79
00:05:32,811 --> 00:05:36,508
''Ross Geller's lunch.
Please don't take me. Okay?''

80
00:05:38,216 --> 00:05:40,480
l'm surprised
you didn't wear it home.

81
00:05:42,320 --> 00:05:44,982
Want to keep your food?
Scare people off.

82
00:05:45,190 --> 00:05:46,748
l learned that on the street.

83
00:05:47,158 --> 00:05:48,147
Really?

84
00:05:48,727 --> 00:05:50,524
What would you say, Pheebs?

85
00:05:50,762 --> 00:05:54,858
Stuff like:
''Keep your mitts off my grub.''

86
00:05:56,434 --> 00:06:00,894
Do you picture Phoebe on the street
with the entire cast of <i>Annie</i>?

87
00:06:03,541 --> 00:06:06,442
This'll keep them away
from your stuff.

88
00:06:12,918 --> 00:06:14,886
Phoebe, you are a badass!

89
00:06:16,421 --> 00:06:19,015
Someday l'll tell you
how l stabbed the cop.

90
00:06:19,958 --> 00:06:21,721
He stabbed me first!

91
00:06:25,797 --> 00:06:29,130
The Brontë sisters were remarkable women
for their time.

92
00:06:29,434 --> 00:06:31,732
They lived in a patriarchal society.

93
00:06:31,970 --> 00:06:33,870
Sorry l'm late,
but l left late.

94
00:06:36,942 --> 00:06:39,536
So, what is the book about?

95
00:06:39,778 --> 00:06:41,473
Didn't you read it
in high school?

96
00:06:41,713 --> 00:06:44,773
l started it, but then
there was this pep rally.

97
00:06:44,983 --> 00:06:46,780
And l was on top of the pyramid.

98
00:06:47,285 --> 00:06:48,775
But anyway...

99
00:06:48,987 --> 00:06:49,976
...what's the book about?

100
00:06:51,256 --> 00:06:54,953
lt's a tragic love story
between Cathy and Heathcliff.

101
00:06:55,226 --> 00:06:58,093
lt takes place on these
creepy moors in England.

102
00:06:58,330 --> 00:07:02,426
Which l think represent the wildness
of Heathcliff's character.

103
00:07:02,667 --> 00:07:04,328
l totally get symbolism.

104
00:07:05,971 --> 00:07:08,997
How would you characterize
the theme of this book?

105
00:07:09,240 --> 00:07:11,140
Let's see....
Rachel Greene?

106
00:07:16,648 --> 00:07:20,516
l would have to say
that it's a tragic love story.

107
00:07:21,119 --> 00:07:23,485
That's sort of a given...

108
00:07:23,688 --> 00:07:25,656
...but, yes.
Anyone else?

109
00:07:26,958 --> 00:07:27,947
Symbolism!

110
00:07:30,996 --> 00:07:33,362
And the wildness of the moors...

111
00:07:33,631 --> 00:07:36,099
...which l think, is mirrored...

112
00:07:36,334 --> 00:07:39,770
...in the wildness
of Heathcliff's character.

113
00:07:41,272 --> 00:07:44,833
Excellent! What Rachel
has shrewdly observed here....

114
00:07:46,344 --> 00:07:48,175
You completely stole my answer!

115
00:07:48,446 --> 00:07:50,175
Honey, that was pretty obvious.

116
00:07:50,448 --> 00:07:52,678
How would you know?
You didn't read it!

117
00:07:54,686 --> 00:07:58,053
What do you think?
You in the blue shirt?

118
00:08:00,725 --> 00:08:05,355
l think that yours is a question
with many possible answers.

119
00:08:06,798 --> 00:08:08,527
Would you care to venture one?

120
00:08:09,300 --> 00:08:11,632
Would you care to venture one?

121
00:08:13,238 --> 00:08:14,967
Are you just repeating me?

122
00:08:15,206 --> 00:08:17,731
Are you just repeating me?

123
00:08:19,978 --> 00:08:21,536
All right. Let's move on.

124
00:08:22,514 --> 00:08:23,503
Okay, then.

125
00:08:27,685 --> 00:08:30,051
Why didn't you say
you hadn't read the book?

126
00:08:30,355 --> 00:08:32,755
l didn't want him
to think l was stupid.

127
00:08:33,024 --> 00:08:36,084
That was really embarrassing,
what happened to you.

128
00:08:40,765 --> 00:08:42,027
Your note?

129
00:08:42,500 --> 00:08:43,489
Amazing!

130
00:08:44,035 --> 00:08:46,367
Not only did no one
touch my sandwich...

131
00:08:46,604 --> 00:08:49,402
...but people at work are
actually afraid of me.

132
00:08:49,941 --> 00:08:51,670
A guy called me ''Mental.''

133
00:08:51,910 --> 00:08:53,377
''Mental Geller.''

134
00:08:53,912 --> 00:08:56,676
l've always wanted
a cool nickname like that.

135
00:08:58,049 --> 00:09:01,610
The best you got in high school
was ''Wet Pants Geller.''

136
00:09:01,853 --> 00:09:03,616
lt was the water fountain, okay?!

137
00:09:05,757 --> 00:09:06,781
Anyway...

138
00:09:08,526 --> 00:09:10,517
...people are writing
reports for me...

139
00:09:10,728 --> 00:09:13,253
...pushing back deadlines
to fit my schedule.

140
00:09:13,531 --> 00:09:15,726
l tell you,
you get tough with people...

141
00:09:15,934 --> 00:09:18,732
...and you can get
anything you want.

142
00:09:18,970 --> 00:09:21,939
Hey, Tribbiani!
Give me that coffee! Now!

143
00:09:31,816 --> 00:09:33,374
This was really fun.

144
00:09:34,886 --> 00:09:36,786
l've been wondering
if you'd ask me out.

145
00:09:37,088 --> 00:09:39,386
So you still wondering?

146
00:09:40,291 --> 00:09:42,452
No. We just went out.

147
00:09:45,630 --> 00:09:46,619
You're smart.

148
00:09:46,898 --> 00:09:48,729
l like that.

149
00:09:55,840 --> 00:09:57,467
Oh, candles!

150
00:09:59,577 --> 00:10:01,135
What is that, a blanket?

151
00:10:01,412 --> 00:10:03,937
A video camera?
Oh, my God!

152
00:10:05,416 --> 00:10:10,513
l can't believe you thought you'd
tape us having sex on the first date!

153
00:10:18,496 --> 00:10:20,657
Joey, is what she just said....

154
00:10:21,966 --> 00:10:23,160
Oh, my God!

155
00:10:23,434 --> 00:10:24,867
You're actually going--

156
00:10:29,774 --> 00:10:31,332
What is going on here?

157
00:10:33,978 --> 00:10:37,209
And with Chandler in the next room.
What are you, sick?

158
00:10:42,620 --> 00:10:43,985
l'm Joey.

159
00:10:47,025 --> 00:10:48,856
l mean, l'm disgusting.

160
00:10:51,496 --> 00:10:53,726
l make low-budget adult films.

161
00:11:05,310 --> 00:11:07,301
You promised to be more careful!

162
00:11:07,579 --> 00:11:10,639
The good Joey name's been
dragged through the mud!

163
00:11:12,884 --> 00:11:13,873
We're so sorry.

164
00:11:14,118 --> 00:11:15,585
l'm telling everyone.

165
00:11:15,787 --> 00:11:20,588
lt's the only explanation that
doesn't make me look like a pig!

166
00:11:20,959 --> 00:11:22,620
No, there's a better explanation.

167
00:11:22,894 --> 00:11:26,352
Tell them you had to make
an adult film for your...

168
00:11:26,564 --> 00:11:28,828
...adult film class.

169
00:11:30,134 --> 00:11:31,761
l like that.
But no!

170
00:11:32,003 --> 00:11:35,302
How does that explain
my underwear at your place?

171
00:11:36,908 --> 00:11:37,966
l don't know.

172
00:11:38,910 --> 00:11:41,777
Get ready to come out
of the non-gay closet.

173
00:11:42,647 --> 00:11:46,105
l promise to come up with something.
Just give us time.

174
00:11:47,485 --> 00:11:48,474
All right.

175
00:11:49,254 --> 00:11:51,814
But it better make me
look really good.

176
00:11:53,191 --> 00:11:54,522
And another thing:

177
00:11:54,993 --> 00:11:56,358
The video camera?

178
00:11:56,661 --> 00:11:57,855
Nice!

179
00:12:07,605 --> 00:12:08,765
May l have a word?

180
00:12:09,007 --> 00:12:10,304
Of course, Donald.

181
00:12:11,175 --> 00:12:15,475
We've been getting reports
of very angry behavior on your part.

182
00:12:15,780 --> 00:12:17,145
-What?
-Threatening letters...

183
00:12:17,448 --> 00:12:19,279
...refusal to meet deadlines.

184
00:12:20,151 --> 00:12:23,120
Apparently people now
call you Mental.

185
00:12:27,492 --> 00:12:30,052
We want you to speak
to a psychiatrist.

186
00:12:32,330 --> 00:12:35,231
You don't understand.
This is so silly.

187
00:12:36,134 --> 00:12:38,659
This is all just
because of a sandwich.

188
00:12:39,804 --> 00:12:41,169
A sandwich?

189
00:12:41,639 --> 00:12:45,973
You see, my sister makes
these amazing turkey sandwiches.

190
00:12:46,311 --> 00:12:51,248
Her secret is, she puts an extra slice
of gravy-soaked bread in the middle.

191
00:12:51,516 --> 00:12:53,347
l call it ''The Moistmaker.''

192
00:12:54,352 --> 00:12:57,344
Anyway, l put my sandwich
in the fridge....

193
00:12:58,356 --> 00:12:59,584
Oh, you know what?

194
00:12:59,857 --> 00:13:01,051
l'm sorry.

195
00:13:01,526 --> 00:13:03,221
l believe l ate that.

196
00:13:07,765 --> 00:13:09,198
You ate my sandwich?

197
00:13:09,734 --> 00:13:11,929
A simple mistake.
lt can happen to anyone.

198
00:13:12,203 --> 00:13:13,227
Oh, really?

199
00:13:15,707 --> 00:13:20,872
Did you confuse it with your own
turkey sandwich with a Moistmaker?

200
00:13:22,947 --> 00:13:24,676
Do you, perhaps, remember...

201
00:13:24,882 --> 00:13:28,443
...seeing a note on top of it?

202
00:13:28,686 --> 00:13:32,747
There may have been a joke
or limerick of some kind.

203
00:13:33,024 --> 00:13:34,855
That said it was...

204
00:13:35,059 --> 00:13:36,890
...my sandwich!

205
00:13:37,762 --> 00:13:39,229
Now, calm down.

206
00:13:39,630 --> 00:13:42,565
Look in my office.
Some may be in the trash.

207
00:13:47,038 --> 00:13:50,405
lt was quite large.
l had to throw most of it away.

208
00:13:52,443 --> 00:13:55,139
You threw my sandwich away?

209
00:13:56,280 --> 00:13:58,145
<i>My sandwich?!</i>

210
00:14:04,088 --> 00:14:05,578
What's this book about?

211
00:14:05,823 --> 00:14:07,154
You didn't read it, either?

212
00:14:07,425 --> 00:14:10,883
l was going to, but l accidentally
read something else.

213
00:14:11,763 --> 00:14:12,957
<i>Vogue.</i>

214
00:14:14,932 --> 00:14:16,763
So tell me about Jane Eyre.

215
00:14:17,001 --> 00:14:18,559
No, read it yourself.

216
00:14:18,770 --> 00:14:21,637
Come on,
don't be such a goody-goody.

217
00:14:22,573 --> 00:14:23,801
Fine.

218
00:14:25,510 --> 00:14:27,137
All right.
So, Jane Eyre?

219
00:14:27,412 --> 00:14:30,006
First, you'd think she's a woman,
but she's not.

220
00:14:30,281 --> 00:14:31,646
She's a cyborg.

221
00:14:34,252 --> 00:14:36,618
A cyborg?
lsn't that like a robot?

222
00:14:37,655 --> 00:14:40,624
This book was light years
ahead of its time.

223
00:14:42,660 --> 00:14:44,628
Sorry l'm late.
Let's get started.

224
00:14:46,164 --> 00:14:48,257
What did you think of <i>Jane Eyre</i>?

225
00:14:48,699 --> 00:14:53,762
Rachel and l were discussing it,
and she had very interesting insights.

226
00:14:55,006 --> 00:14:56,439
Go ahead, Rachel.

227
00:14:57,875 --> 00:14:59,103
Thank you, Phoebe.

228
00:15:01,212 --> 00:15:04,272
What struck me most
when reading <i>Jane Eyre</i>...

229
00:15:04,482 --> 00:15:07,645
...was how the book was
so ahead of its time.

230
00:15:07,885 --> 00:15:11,685
lf you're talking about feminism,
l think you're right.

231
00:15:13,724 --> 00:15:17,182
Well, feminism, yes.
But also the robots.

232
00:15:25,236 --> 00:15:28,034
Since that video camera thing
didn't work out...

233
00:15:28,973 --> 00:15:33,342
...l thought that l would give you
just a little preview.

234
00:15:34,712 --> 00:15:36,077
You're naked!

235
00:15:36,347 --> 00:15:37,371
l know!

236
00:15:56,167 --> 00:15:57,395
Are you okay?

237
00:15:57,668 --> 00:15:59,033
l'm fine.

238
00:15:59,270 --> 00:16:01,932
l saw a psychiatrist at work today.

239
00:16:02,373 --> 00:16:03,362
Why?

240
00:16:03,708 --> 00:16:05,608
On account of my rage.

241
00:16:06,711 --> 00:16:10,374
Which, if l may say,
right now is out of control.

242
00:16:11,249 --> 00:16:13,945
He gave me a pill for it.

243
00:16:15,353 --> 00:16:16,445
A pill?

244
00:16:16,787 --> 00:16:20,188
When the psychiatrist told me
to take a leave of absence...

245
00:16:20,424 --> 00:16:24,724
...because l yelled at my boss,
l started to get worked up again.

246
00:16:24,962 --> 00:16:27,624
So he offered me a tranquilizer.

247
00:16:27,865 --> 00:16:30,129
And l thought it was a good idea.

248
00:16:30,368 --> 00:16:31,926
So l took it.

249
00:16:33,938 --> 00:16:36,702
They're making you take
time off work?

250
00:16:36,941 --> 00:16:38,272
And you're okay with that?

251
00:16:38,609 --> 00:16:40,042
l don't know.

252
00:16:40,645 --> 00:16:44,103
lt's going to be weird
not having a job for a while.

253
00:16:44,415 --> 00:16:47,543
But l definitely don't care
about my sandwich.

254
00:16:49,420 --> 00:16:52,150
l hate it when they make me see
the shrink at my office.

255
00:16:52,323 --> 00:16:57,192
He's always like, ''Your colleagues will
like you better if you like yourself better.''

256
00:16:57,361 --> 00:16:58,919
Who needs that?

257
00:16:59,096 --> 00:17:01,496
-You do.
-l know.

258
00:17:03,334 --> 00:17:07,828
lt's so embarrassing! l can't believe
you let me go on like that!

259
00:17:08,039 --> 00:17:09,438
l'm sorry.

260
00:17:11,909 --> 00:17:15,572
lt was so funny when you compared
<i>Jane Eyre</i> to <i>Robocop.</i>

261
00:17:17,748 --> 00:17:19,841
That was not funny!

262
00:17:20,084 --> 00:17:23,679
l snapped, okay?
You weren't taking the class seriously.

263
00:17:23,955 --> 00:17:25,889
Come on!
What is the big deal?

264
00:17:26,090 --> 00:17:28,820
l thought it'd be something
we could do together.

265
00:17:29,126 --> 00:17:30,457
l thought it would be fun.

266
00:17:30,695 --> 00:17:32,026
Fun is good.

267
00:17:32,263 --> 00:17:34,254
But l also wanted to learn.

268
00:17:34,498 --> 00:17:38,992
People talk about what they learned
in high school. l never went.

269
00:17:41,606 --> 00:17:44,166
So you really wanted to learn.

270
00:17:46,277 --> 00:17:49,212
You know, Pheebs,
l just wanted to have fun.

271
00:17:50,181 --> 00:17:51,546
You know who should go?

272
00:17:51,816 --> 00:17:53,875
l know! l know! l know!

273
00:17:55,553 --> 00:17:58,351
Monica, you asked the question.

274
00:18:17,108 --> 00:18:19,406
Oh, my God, that's Monica!

275
00:18:23,080 --> 00:18:26,413
You get away from me,
you sick, sick, sicko!

276
00:18:27,251 --> 00:18:28,411
What's going on?

277
00:18:29,020 --> 00:18:31,045
Joey has got a secret peephole!

278
00:18:33,157 --> 00:18:36,354
-Oh, no!
-Yes, he has a naked picture of Monica!

279
00:18:36,594 --> 00:18:40,121
He takes naked pictures of us, then
he eats chicken and looks at them!

280
00:18:44,201 --> 00:18:46,169
Oh! Dude, that's my sister!

281
00:18:46,404 --> 00:18:47,701
Give me that!

282
00:18:47,972 --> 00:18:50,304
Wait! Everybody calm down, okay?

283
00:18:50,541 --> 00:18:54,841
Let's give our friend a chance
to explain why he's such a big pervert!

284
00:18:56,647 --> 00:18:58,638
l am not a pervert, okay?

285
00:18:58,849 --> 00:19:00,214
lt's just....

286
00:19:00,484 --> 00:19:01,473
l just kind of....

287
00:19:03,087 --> 00:19:05,248
l think l can explain this.

288
00:19:05,556 --> 00:19:06,818
Thank you.

289
00:19:08,159 --> 00:19:09,990
Joey's a sex addict.

290
00:19:11,429 --> 00:19:13,158
What?! No, l'm not!

291
00:19:13,397 --> 00:19:15,558
lt's okay! lt's good!

292
00:19:17,334 --> 00:19:19,199
lt's a disease.

293
00:19:20,004 --> 00:19:21,733
l am not a sex addict!

294
00:19:22,006 --> 00:19:23,405
Yes, you are!

295
00:19:24,341 --> 00:19:26,809
That's the only way
to explain all this stuff!

296
00:19:27,011 --> 00:19:28,774
No, it isn't. lt's not.

297
00:19:29,013 --> 00:19:31,573
Because you could also explain it
with the truth!

298
00:19:32,783 --> 00:19:33,909
What is the truth?

299
00:19:34,118 --> 00:19:35,881
-What's up?
-What's going on?

300
00:19:41,859 --> 00:19:43,759
l slept with Monica.

301
00:19:49,967 --> 00:19:53,459
Well, let's see what everybody
thinks of that.

302
00:19:59,376 --> 00:20:01,367
You slept with my sister?

303
00:20:02,480 --> 00:20:03,947
Yes, but it was--

304
00:20:04,215 --> 00:20:06,274
We just did it once, in London.

305
00:20:06,784 --> 00:20:09,309
This is not good for my rage.

306
00:20:14,325 --> 00:20:15,383
ls this true?

307
00:20:15,626 --> 00:20:16,888
Of course, it's true.

308
00:20:17,895 --> 00:20:22,059
How else would you explain all the
weird stuff that's been going on?

309
00:20:23,634 --> 00:20:24,623
Yes, it's true.

310
00:20:27,171 --> 00:20:30,663
lf it happened once, how come we
found your underwear in our apartment?

311
00:20:33,978 --> 00:20:37,072
That was the underwear
l was wearing that night in London.

312
00:20:37,314 --> 00:20:38,645
Right, Monica?

313
00:20:41,986 --> 00:20:43,954
l guess l wanted to keep it...

314
00:20:45,256 --> 00:20:46,416
...as a souvenir.

315
00:20:48,692 --> 00:20:50,319
My God, Monica!

316
00:20:51,362 --> 00:20:54,661
Are you sure you're not
just a sex addict?

317
00:20:57,768 --> 00:21:00,965
lf anyone's a sex addict here,
it's Monica.

318
00:21:02,506 --> 00:21:06,135
She has been trying to get me back
in the sack ever since London!

319
00:21:07,178 --> 00:21:10,045
That's why she gave you
a naked picture of herself.

320
00:21:10,281 --> 00:21:11,680
That makes sense.

321
00:21:13,217 --> 00:21:14,707
And the video camera?

322
00:21:19,490 --> 00:21:23,688
l guess l set up the video camera
to try and entice Joey.

323
00:21:25,029 --> 00:21:27,964
But, sadly, l could not be enticed.

324
00:21:29,700 --> 00:21:33,101
Monica, this has to stop now.

325
00:21:34,672 --> 00:21:36,264
l know, l know.

326
00:21:36,440 --> 00:21:40,934
l know. l will, and l would appreciate
if we all could just...

327
00:21:41,111 --> 00:21:44,774
...drop it immediately, and forever.

328
00:21:45,182 --> 00:21:48,709
Okay. That is, if you can resist me.

329
00:21:50,354 --> 00:21:53,551
-l'll give it my best shot.
-Good luck.

330
00:21:54,792 --> 00:21:56,020
Unbelievable!

331
00:21:56,293 --> 00:21:58,921
You really kept Joey's underwear?

332
00:21:59,196 --> 00:22:01,630
Why? Why would you do that?

333
00:22:05,502 --> 00:22:06,867
l'm Monica.

334
00:22:08,038 --> 00:22:09,471
l'm disgusting.

335
00:22:11,342 --> 00:22:14,106
l stalk guys and keep their underpants.

336
00:22:19,316 --> 00:22:23,218
l think we've all learned
who's disgusting and who's not.

337
00:22:26,223 --> 00:22:29,192
Now, l'm going to get back
to my bucket.

338
00:22:30,661 --> 00:22:33,858
l'm only eating the skin,
so the chicken's up for grabs.

339
00:22:39,803 --> 00:22:41,794
You were making a good point.

340
00:22:42,072 --> 00:22:43,972
l mean, till you got cut off.

341
00:22:44,742 --> 00:22:46,676
What's up with that girl Monica?

342
00:22:46,944 --> 00:22:48,775
l don't know.
l didn't come with her.

343
00:22:50,848 --> 00:22:53,316
Hey, everybody!
Everybody, guess what!

344
00:22:53,584 --> 00:22:55,848
l just convinced Carl
to give us a test.

345
00:22:56,086 --> 00:22:57,144
Test?

346
00:22:57,421 --> 00:23:00,254
Come on!
Tests make us all better learners!

347
00:23:02,426 --> 00:23:05,088
Oh, yeah!
We should have essay questions!

348
00:23:07,364 --> 00:23:08,353
[ENGLlSH]

