1
00:00:12,090 --> 00:00:13,648
You look cute in bubbles.

2
00:00:13,926 --> 00:00:16,292
You're just all liquored up.

3
00:00:19,431 --> 00:00:21,490
Hey, it's me. l'm coming in.

4
00:00:28,507 --> 00:00:30,998
l've had a very long, hard day.

5
00:00:33,312 --> 00:00:36,475
-You're home early.
-Yeah, my date threw up.

6
00:00:37,716 --> 00:00:39,047
Want some chicken?

7
00:00:39,217 --> 00:00:41,276
No, thanks. No chicken.
Bye-bye.

8
00:00:43,188 --> 00:00:45,622
You sure?
Some extra-crispy, dirty rice?

9
00:00:45,857 --> 00:00:48,189
For the last time, no!
Get out, Joey!

10
00:00:48,393 --> 00:00:49,792
All right.

11
00:00:53,966 --> 00:00:55,763
Are you okay?
He wouldn't leave.

12
00:00:56,034 --> 00:00:58,434
He kept asking me if l wanted chicken.

13
00:00:58,737 --> 00:00:59,897
Chicken?

14
00:01:01,206 --> 00:01:02,798
l could eat some chicken.

15
00:01:08,547 --> 00:01:13,075
Could l get a three-piece,
some coleslaw, some beans and a Coke?

16
00:01:13,318 --> 00:01:14,785
Diet Coke.

17
00:01:19,791 --> 00:01:21,554
The One With All the Kissing

18
00:01:58,930 --> 00:02:01,797
-Morning, Pheebs.
-l have to tell you this story.

19
00:02:02,000 --> 00:02:04,298
l was coming over
and this cabdriver--

20
00:02:04,536 --> 00:02:05,628
Was his name Angus?

21
00:02:07,272 --> 00:02:08,296
What?

22
00:02:08,540 --> 00:02:10,804
He was a cabdriver
we had in London.

23
00:02:12,811 --> 00:02:14,438
All right. Anyway--

24
00:02:14,680 --> 00:02:16,944
What was that pub he took us to?

25
00:02:17,182 --> 00:02:18,342
The Wheat Sheaf!

26
00:02:18,617 --> 00:02:20,175
And they had that beer....

27
00:02:20,385 --> 00:02:22,012
Boddington's!

28
00:02:25,223 --> 00:02:27,350
Pheebs was going to tell a story.

29
00:02:27,559 --> 00:02:30,289
So he had a really funny hat.

30
00:02:30,562 --> 00:02:32,826
l don't want to talk about it.

31
00:02:34,566 --> 00:02:36,397
-Hey.
-Hey, Ross!

32
00:02:36,835 --> 00:02:38,632
Boddington's!

33
00:02:38,870 --> 00:02:40,303
Oh, man!

34
00:02:41,540 --> 00:02:45,738
l'd walk back to London for another
frosty one of those bad boys.

35
00:02:46,011 --> 00:02:49,037
They have them at the
British pub by the Trade Center.

36
00:02:49,347 --> 00:02:50,712
Later!

37
00:02:51,817 --> 00:02:53,341
Shouldn't Rachel be back?

38
00:02:53,585 --> 00:02:55,052
Her plane got delayed.

39
00:02:55,353 --> 00:02:57,082
But she should be here by now.

40
00:02:57,322 --> 00:03:00,052
So you talked to her?
Did she sound mad?

41
00:03:00,492 --> 00:03:02,221
No. But she likes me.

42
00:03:03,562 --> 00:03:05,325
You abandoned her
on a plane to Greece.

43
00:03:05,564 --> 00:03:08,431
l did not ''abandon'' Rachel. Okay?

44
00:03:08,700 --> 00:03:10,565
Emily showed up at the airport.

45
00:03:10,769 --> 00:03:13,863
l had to go after her.
l did what l had to do.

46
00:03:14,106 --> 00:03:16,574
She's my wife.
Rachel is my wife.

47
00:03:16,842 --> 00:03:18,002
Emily!

48
00:03:19,878 --> 00:03:22,608
Emily is my wife.

49
00:03:23,181 --> 00:03:25,115
Man, what is that?

50
00:03:26,184 --> 00:03:28,049
You haven't heard from Emily?

51
00:03:28,253 --> 00:03:30,346
Not since l lost her at the airport.

52
00:03:30,589 --> 00:03:32,580
l can't believe she can outrun you.

53
00:03:32,858 --> 00:03:35,349
Hey! She's fast, okay?

54
00:03:35,927 --> 00:03:39,522
You think you can beat me?
Let's go! Outside!

55
00:03:41,900 --> 00:03:44,698
-l'm sorry. l'm just a little--
-Slow?

56
00:03:44,870 --> 00:03:46,735
Oh, you want some?!

57
00:03:46,905 --> 00:03:50,136
Okay, get the shoes on! Let's go, man!

58
00:03:50,308 --> 00:03:52,173
lt's cool, okay?

59
00:03:52,344 --> 00:03:54,744
You're the fastest!

60
00:03:55,747 --> 00:03:58,477
-Hi!
-Oh, my God, Rachel!

61
00:03:59,651 --> 00:04:04,247
Rach, l am so sorry.
l am so, so sorry.

62
00:04:04,523 --> 00:04:07,014
Come on.
You just did what you had to do.

63
00:04:09,528 --> 00:04:12,929
That's it? You're not mad?
lt must've been terrible.

64
00:04:13,131 --> 00:04:15,190
Terrible? Hell, l was in Greece!

65
00:04:16,334 --> 00:04:20,134
There was a nice hotel, nice beach,
met the nice people.

66
00:04:20,372 --> 00:04:22,602
lt's not too shabby for Rachel.

67
00:04:25,677 --> 00:04:27,304
So, what, that's it?

68
00:04:28,947 --> 00:04:31,609
We're cool. Totally cool.

69
00:04:32,384 --> 00:04:34,113
Thanks, Rach.
You're the best.

70
00:04:34,319 --> 00:04:36,651
Oh, no. You're the best.

71
00:04:38,123 --> 00:04:40,717
Oh, l got to go to the flower store.

72
00:04:41,660 --> 00:04:44,288
No one will tell me where Emily is...

73
00:04:44,529 --> 00:04:48,659
...so l'm sending 72 long-stemmed, red
roses to her parents' house.

74
00:04:48,900 --> 00:04:51,835
One for each day
l've known and loved her.

75
00:04:52,037 --> 00:04:53,698
That should get her talking.

76
00:04:53,905 --> 00:04:58,239
When you make out the card,
be sure to make it out to ''Emily.''

77
00:05:02,881 --> 00:05:05,714
lt's good that you had
such a good time in Greece.

78
00:05:06,918 --> 00:05:08,044
What?

79
00:05:09,688 --> 00:05:11,986
l didn't have a good time in Greece!

80
00:05:12,724 --> 00:05:14,919
Ross abandoned me!

81
00:05:15,160 --> 00:05:19,358
l couldn't get a plane out.
l had to stay in their suite!

82
00:05:19,598 --> 00:05:24,535
People came up to me going,
''Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?''

83
00:05:24,936 --> 00:05:28,235
l mean, it was so humiliating!

84
00:05:28,440 --> 00:05:30,567
l felt like such an idiot!

85
00:05:30,775 --> 00:05:33,107
lt's all my fault.
You know why?

86
00:05:33,345 --> 00:05:36,712
Because l make very bad decisions.

87
00:05:36,915 --> 00:05:38,109
Oh, that's not true.

88
00:05:38,416 --> 00:05:41,852
Yes, it is true.
l went after Ross in stupid London!

89
00:05:42,087 --> 00:05:44,885
London is stupid! Stupid!

90
00:05:46,191 --> 00:05:49,456
l put on a cheerleading outfit
to seduce Joshua.

91
00:05:49,628 --> 00:05:54,292
Then l lost him because l asked him
to marry me after four dates.

92
00:05:54,466 --> 00:05:58,800
And then l went to Greece
on somebody else's honeymoon. Okay?

93
00:05:58,970 --> 00:06:02,269
Do those sound like very good
decisions to you?

94
00:06:02,774 --> 00:06:04,935
l like your little braid.

95
00:06:05,710 --> 00:06:07,871
l just shouldn't be allowed
to make decisions anymore.

96
00:06:08,046 --> 00:06:10,708
Phoebe, you were right.
l should've never gone to London.

97
00:06:10,949 --> 00:06:14,282
From now on, you make
all my decisions for me.

98
00:06:14,452 --> 00:06:16,943
Oh, no.
l did that for someone once.

99
00:06:17,188 --> 00:06:21,147
l'm not comfortable having
that power over someone's life.

100
00:06:21,359 --> 00:06:22,724
l'll do it.

101
00:06:24,262 --> 00:06:27,925
Fine. Monica, you are now
in charge of my love life.

102
00:06:29,200 --> 00:06:30,895
Okay. l got to go to work.

103
00:06:41,379 --> 00:06:43,574
And Rachel, great to have you back.

104
00:06:55,860 --> 00:06:57,225
Always a pleasure.

105
00:07:06,204 --> 00:07:08,229
Rachel? Sweetie, look.

106
00:07:08,440 --> 00:07:10,908
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.

107
00:07:11,142 --> 00:07:12,404
He's married.

108
00:07:12,644 --> 00:07:15,545
Ross is married.
l still can't believe it.

109
00:07:16,214 --> 00:07:18,444
Honey, sweetie, by the edges.

110
00:07:19,117 --> 00:07:20,846
l'll just have to accept it.

111
00:07:21,052 --> 00:07:22,713
l mean, it's my fault.

112
00:07:23,288 --> 00:07:25,313
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!

113
00:07:25,557 --> 00:07:27,491
Oh, my God!

114
00:07:32,297 --> 00:07:35,596
That's okay. l know that
you're very upset right now.

115
00:07:35,800 --> 00:07:37,597
l know that wasn't about me.

116
00:07:37,902 --> 00:07:39,893
l bet it was about her a little.

117
00:07:40,338 --> 00:07:42,636
lf you'd stop thinking about Ross...

118
00:07:42,841 --> 00:07:45,742
...you'd notice there are
great guys everywhere.

119
00:07:45,977 --> 00:07:47,069
Look. Gunther.

120
00:07:49,981 --> 00:07:51,573
He's nice. He's cute.

121
00:07:52,117 --> 00:07:54,142
Yeah. l guess Gunther is....

122
00:07:54,486 --> 00:07:56,386
What about that guy over there?

123
00:07:57,589 --> 00:08:00,387
That's the guy you flirted with
at the counter.

124
00:08:01,826 --> 00:08:04,954
-Oh, l don't know. l don't know.
-You're going to talk to him.

125
00:08:05,230 --> 00:08:08,825
l make your decisions,
and l say you're going to talk to him.

126
00:08:09,768 --> 00:08:10,928
All right.

127
00:08:11,136 --> 00:08:14,299
You're the boss.
l got to do what you tell me.

128
00:08:14,572 --> 00:08:16,767
Say that to him, and you're golden.

129
00:08:22,847 --> 00:08:25,748
Hey, Pheebs.
We got our pictures back from London.

130
00:08:25,984 --> 00:08:28,680
Here's all of us
at the Tower of London....

131
00:08:29,154 --> 00:08:30,781
Here we all are.

132
00:08:31,256 --> 00:08:33,747
There's Ross and Joey and you and--

133
00:08:35,293 --> 00:08:36,317
And me.

134
00:08:38,129 --> 00:08:40,427
We've been talking about
London too much.

135
00:08:40,932 --> 00:08:43,696
Sorry, it's just because
l couldn't be there.

136
00:08:44,002 --> 00:08:47,460
All l get to do now is pregnant stuff.
lt bums me out.

137
00:08:47,672 --> 00:08:49,139
-l'm sorry.
-Sorry.

138
00:08:50,375 --> 00:08:52,605
Know what l like to do?
lt sounds a little corny...

139
00:08:52,777 --> 00:08:55,974
...but sometimes when l'm bummed out,
l like to just close my eyes...

140
00:08:56,147 --> 00:08:58,741
...and think about
what a wonderful gift life is.

141
00:09:06,891 --> 00:09:08,483
See?

142
00:09:11,129 --> 00:09:14,223
-What happened?
-A little of this, a little of that.

143
00:09:14,499 --> 00:09:16,126
l got myself a date tomorrow.

144
00:09:16,434 --> 00:09:20,393
See? Didn't l tell you?
You're getting over Ross already.

145
00:09:22,006 --> 00:09:22,995
Get out.

146
00:09:39,090 --> 00:09:40,079
What took so long?

147
00:09:40,358 --> 00:09:43,657
l got caught up at work.
But l'm quitting tomorrow.

148
00:09:48,666 --> 00:09:50,861
So thanks for having me over.

149
00:10:08,887 --> 00:10:10,377
See you, man.

150
00:10:13,391 --> 00:10:15,188
What the hell was that?

151
00:10:15,793 --> 00:10:20,025
Probably some European
goodbye thing he picked up in London.

152
00:10:20,298 --> 00:10:21,856
That's not European.

153
00:10:22,700 --> 00:10:24,292
lt felt French.

154
00:10:26,871 --> 00:10:30,534
Well, l guess it's time for me
to say goodbye too, <i>mon frère.</i>

155
00:10:32,243 --> 00:10:34,803
Come here and give me a little sugar.

156
00:10:40,985 --> 00:10:42,782
l really had a good time.

157
00:10:43,021 --> 00:10:44,386
Yeah, me too.

158
00:10:47,959 --> 00:10:49,017
l guess this is it.

159
00:10:51,663 --> 00:10:53,722
Unless you want to come inside?

160
00:10:56,301 --> 00:11:00,032
Wait a minute. You know what?
l can't decide this.

161
00:11:02,473 --> 00:11:04,373
Okay. Just hold on a second.

162
00:11:11,049 --> 00:11:13,449
Where's Monica?
l have to ask her something.

163
00:11:13,651 --> 00:11:15,050
Doing her laundry.

164
00:11:15,653 --> 00:11:16,881
What's that?

165
00:11:17,689 --> 00:11:19,748
lt came in the mail today.

166
00:11:21,092 --> 00:11:23,526
lt's 72 long-stemmed red roses.

167
00:11:23,728 --> 00:11:26,663
One for each day
l've known and loved Emily...

168
00:11:26,864 --> 00:11:29,025
...cut up into mulch.

169
00:11:31,069 --> 00:11:32,764
Honey, that's awful.

170
00:11:33,905 --> 00:11:34,894
lt's not so bad.

171
00:11:35,106 --> 00:11:37,540
Monica's going to make potpourri.

172
00:11:40,678 --> 00:11:45,012
l think l'm going to go
wander out in the rain for a while.

173
00:11:45,216 --> 00:11:46,240
lt's not raining.

174
00:11:46,517 --> 00:11:49,008
l can't catch a break!

175
00:11:50,421 --> 00:11:53,686
You're not going anywhere.
Sit right here.

176
00:11:53,958 --> 00:11:57,018
l'll make you some tea
and we'll talk this out.

177
00:11:57,295 --> 00:11:58,387
All right?

178
00:12:02,200 --> 00:12:03,394
Hey, Dave.

179
00:12:04,235 --> 00:12:08,194
l need to take a rain check.
My roommate is really sick.

180
00:12:08,439 --> 00:12:09,428
Okay. Bye!

181
00:12:13,211 --> 00:12:14,701
Honey, listen.

182
00:12:15,446 --> 00:12:18,540
l know things seem so
bad...

183
00:12:18,750 --> 00:12:21,082
...and that they won't get any--

184
00:12:21,586 --> 00:12:23,144
Could l talk to you?

185
00:12:24,589 --> 00:12:26,147
l dropped some socks.

186
00:12:35,833 --> 00:12:40,566
What is the matter with you?
Do you want to fall into the trap?

187
00:12:40,805 --> 00:12:43,603
You did not drop any socks!

188
00:12:43,908 --> 00:12:46,103
l saw Dave, and he said
you blew him off!

189
00:12:46,277 --> 00:12:47,266
You listen to me!

190
00:12:47,478 --> 00:12:51,414
l'm calling the shots!
l say you leave Ross and go get Dave.

191
00:12:51,616 --> 00:12:52,742
What are you doing?

192
00:12:52,950 --> 00:12:56,943
Well, ultimately l was trying,
you know, l wanted...

193
00:12:57,822 --> 00:13:00,416
...to tell him that
l'm still in love with him.

194
00:13:00,792 --> 00:13:03,784
What? You cannot tell him that!

195
00:13:04,028 --> 00:13:05,359
Why? Why not?

196
00:13:05,596 --> 00:13:07,655
People love to hear that!

197
00:13:08,566 --> 00:13:10,227
Come on, l love you.

198
00:13:10,401 --> 00:13:12,130
-Wasn't that nice?
-No.

199
00:13:12,303 --> 00:13:14,635
l make the decisions and l say no!

200
00:13:14,806 --> 00:13:18,401
You know what? No, you don't
make my decisions, because...

201
00:13:18,710 --> 00:13:20,075
...you're fired.

202
00:13:20,411 --> 00:13:22,072
You can't fire me.

203
00:13:22,347 --> 00:13:26,841
l make your decisions,
and l say l'm not fired! Ha!

204
00:13:29,087 --> 00:13:30,247
Well....

205
00:13:40,665 --> 00:13:41,996
Come on, let me in!

206
00:13:42,233 --> 00:13:43,723
Having some trouble?

207
00:13:44,936 --> 00:13:46,267
Rachel locked the door.

208
00:13:46,504 --> 00:13:49,496
l'll kick that door in
if you give me some sugar.

209
00:13:51,909 --> 00:13:55,174
Ross, there's something
l wanna talk to you about.

210
00:13:55,346 --> 00:13:58,838
-l just need to--
-Rachel, open this door!

211
00:13:59,016 --> 00:14:02,315
-What, is it locked?
-She's fine. Listen....

212
00:14:02,620 --> 00:14:05,145
Rachel, l can do this all night if l have to!

213
00:14:05,323 --> 00:14:07,883
-You want me to get that?
-No. Just let her do her thing...

214
00:14:08,059 --> 00:14:11,586
...and we'll do our thing.
Because l really need to tell you--

215
00:14:18,936 --> 00:14:20,028
Thank you.

216
00:14:22,907 --> 00:14:25,535
Rachel? Can l talk to you
outside for a sec?

217
00:14:28,713 --> 00:14:29,941
We really need to talk.

218
00:14:30,248 --> 00:14:31,681
Well, then talk.

219
00:14:32,350 --> 00:14:33,942
Okay, l will.

220
00:14:36,954 --> 00:14:41,118
Remember that thing we just discussed
that you wanted to do?

221
00:14:41,559 --> 00:14:42,617
What thing?

222
00:14:46,230 --> 00:14:48,755
Rachel wants to take
swing dance lessons.

223
00:14:49,434 --> 00:14:51,959
Which l think is a really stupid idea.

224
00:14:52,236 --> 00:14:55,296
lt's dangerous.
She won't get what she wants.

225
00:14:55,540 --> 00:14:58,532
And who knows who she might
end up hurting?

226
00:15:04,882 --> 00:15:08,249
Monica's right.
Swing dancing can be tricky.

227
00:15:10,421 --> 00:15:11,718
l have to use the phone.

228
00:15:11,989 --> 00:15:15,891
l gotta cancel those five giant
teddy bears l sent to Emily.

229
00:15:16,160 --> 00:15:18,594
My God! Think of the massacre.

230
00:15:19,730 --> 00:15:20,890
l'm going to do it.

231
00:15:21,132 --> 00:15:22,929
l know you think l'm crazy.

232
00:15:23,134 --> 00:15:26,262
But before you tell him,
try to find one person...

233
00:15:26,471 --> 00:15:28,803
...who thinks it's a good idea.
l bet you can't.

234
00:15:29,006 --> 00:15:30,098
Please?

235
00:15:32,343 --> 00:15:33,640
All right. Fine.

236
00:15:38,182 --> 00:15:40,082
Joey! l'm in!

237
00:15:40,318 --> 00:15:42,411
All right. Good deal.

238
00:15:49,694 --> 00:15:52,128
-Hi.
-Hey, Rach.

239
00:15:52,296 --> 00:15:54,821
-Did you find anyone who agrees with you?
-No.

240
00:15:54,999 --> 00:15:58,560
But you know what?
l think l need a male point of view.

241
00:15:59,670 --> 00:16:01,194
Joey.

242
00:16:03,140 --> 00:16:06,541
-You're a man.
-You got that right.

243
00:16:06,978 --> 00:16:10,880
Do you think it would be a good idea
if l told Ross that l was still in love with him?

244
00:16:11,048 --> 00:16:12,174
Nope.

245
00:16:14,652 --> 00:16:17,246
-Pheebs!
-Hey, Pheebs.

246
00:16:21,125 --> 00:16:22,752
-Pheebs?
-Yeah.

247
00:16:22,927 --> 00:16:26,419
You know how you were saying
you didn't get to go to London...

248
00:16:26,664 --> 00:16:28,495
...and you were feeling left out?

249
00:16:28,699 --> 00:16:31,532
Well, we all felt really bad
about that...

250
00:16:31,836 --> 00:16:35,203
...so we decided to
take a little trip together!

251
00:16:35,640 --> 00:16:37,608
Oh, that's so nice!

252
00:16:37,875 --> 00:16:39,638
How great!
Where's the trip?

253
00:16:40,177 --> 00:16:43,374
Well, we thought we would all
go to a picnic...

254
00:16:44,348 --> 00:16:45,713
...in Central Park!

255
00:16:45,950 --> 00:16:47,474
Central Park?

256
00:16:48,286 --> 00:16:49,844
All of us. All day.

257
00:16:50,454 --> 00:16:51,478
That sucks!

258
00:16:52,857 --> 00:16:55,121
That's not a trip!
l just came from there.

259
00:16:55,459 --> 00:16:58,326
What'll we high-five about
at the stupid park?

260
00:16:58,629 --> 00:17:01,496
lt's right by my house.
All right!

261
00:17:03,334 --> 00:17:07,293
l'm going home to bask in the
triumph of my Central Park idea.

262
00:17:08,472 --> 00:17:10,531
Hold on a sec there, Mr. Kissy.

263
00:17:12,343 --> 00:17:14,072
l wanted to talk to you about...

264
00:17:14,312 --> 00:17:17,509
...this whole new European thing
you've got going on.

265
00:17:17,715 --> 00:17:20,843
And l need to say
it makes me very uncomfortable...

266
00:17:21,085 --> 00:17:23,553
...and l just, you know, just stop it!

267
00:17:24,822 --> 00:17:27,256
Just bringing some culture
to the group.

268
00:17:27,658 --> 00:17:30,388
That's fine.
Just don't bring it in my mouth.

269
00:17:31,095 --> 00:17:32,892
lt makes me want to puke.

270
00:17:39,904 --> 00:17:42,236
Hey, everybody!
Pheebs is here!

271
00:17:44,775 --> 00:17:47,335
-Phoebe! Woo!
-Okay. Woo! Hi!

272
00:17:48,512 --> 00:17:52,278
Pheebs, we decided that
the picnic idea was a little....

273
00:17:52,516 --> 00:17:54,882
lt didn't have any....
Well, it blew.

274
00:17:57,355 --> 00:18:01,849
We thought that this afternoon we'd
all go away for the whole weekend...

275
00:18:02,059 --> 00:18:03,390
...to Atlantic City.

276
00:18:03,594 --> 00:18:08,031
Atlantic City! Oh, that's
a great plan! Whose plan was that?

277
00:18:08,199 --> 00:18:09,188
Mine!

278
00:18:10,201 --> 00:18:13,193
-Wait. lt was my plan.
-No...

279
00:18:13,437 --> 00:18:15,769
...l said we needed a new plan.

280
00:18:16,040 --> 00:18:18,031
And l came up with Atlantic City.

281
00:18:18,242 --> 00:18:20,267
Which is the new plan.

282
00:18:23,280 --> 00:18:25,748
Why don't we all
meet upstairs in an hour.

283
00:18:27,551 --> 00:18:31,043
l'm going to go pack.
l'm going to go pack my ass off.

284
00:18:32,857 --> 00:18:37,157
Well, l think l'm gonna grab some coffee
because my ass is already packed.

285
00:18:41,232 --> 00:18:42,221
Let's go.

286
00:18:42,466 --> 00:18:44,957
You know what?
l'll meet you in a minute.

287
00:18:45,503 --> 00:18:49,132
Rachel, you didn't find anyone,
so you can't tell him.

288
00:18:49,407 --> 00:18:51,500
You know what?
That doesn't matter.

289
00:18:52,643 --> 00:18:56,409
Do you know how painful it is
to tell someone you love them...

290
00:18:56,647 --> 00:18:58,444
...and not have them say it back?

291
00:19:00,418 --> 00:19:02,249
l don't care.

292
00:19:06,090 --> 00:19:07,785
l can't watch.

293
00:19:22,673 --> 00:19:24,106
What you reading?

294
00:19:25,509 --> 00:19:26,498
Paper.

295
00:19:26,677 --> 00:19:28,474
Yeah? What's it about?

296
00:19:30,448 --> 00:19:33,144
Events from around the globe.

297
00:19:38,355 --> 00:19:40,983
There's something
l have to talk to you about.

298
00:19:41,192 --> 00:19:42,853
Everyone's saying l shouldn't.

299
00:19:43,127 --> 00:19:45,994
But l think they're wrong.
People can be wrong.

300
00:19:46,630 --> 00:19:47,858
Once at work...

301
00:19:48,132 --> 00:19:50,726
...l thought carbon dating
is fossilized--

302
00:19:51,001 --> 00:19:53,697
l'm really trying to tell
you something here.

303
00:19:56,240 --> 00:19:57,502
Go ahead.

304
00:19:59,009 --> 00:20:01,204
l think l'm just going to say it.

305
00:20:01,479 --> 00:20:02,878
l'm just going to say it.

306
00:20:11,856 --> 00:20:15,451
l'm still in love with you, Ross.

307
00:20:30,875 --> 00:20:33,776
l'm not sure what to do
with that right now.

308
00:20:39,517 --> 00:20:42,418
What? Was that a joke?
Because it's mean.

309
00:20:45,156 --> 00:20:47,351
l'm so dead serious!

310
00:20:47,958 --> 00:20:49,482
l'm totally serious!

311
00:20:49,693 --> 00:20:50,990
Why are you laughing?

312
00:20:53,664 --> 00:20:55,655
Because l just heard it!

313
00:20:55,933 --> 00:20:57,924
l heard it. And it's ridiculous!

314
00:20:58,169 --> 00:20:59,295
l mean....

315
00:20:59,603 --> 00:21:00,763
You're married!

316
00:21:01,105 --> 00:21:03,471
You're married,
and it's just ridiculous!

317
00:21:03,707 --> 00:21:07,199
When l said it, l sort of
floated up out of my body.

318
00:21:07,478 --> 00:21:12,211
And then l heard myself say it,
and then the floating Rachel....

319
00:21:14,985 --> 00:21:18,352
l was like, ''You are such an idiot!''

320
00:21:22,459 --> 00:21:24,984
-Well, l am married.
-l know.

321
00:21:25,729 --> 00:21:28,789
Though l haven't spoken to her
since the wedding.

322
00:21:32,303 --> 00:21:34,498
l'm sorry. That's not funny.

323
00:21:35,906 --> 00:21:38,966
Actually, it kind of is.

324
00:21:41,645 --> 00:21:43,738
My wife won't return my calls.

325
00:21:47,084 --> 00:21:49,314
l don't know where my wife is.

326
00:21:52,590 --> 00:21:55,753
''Hey, Ross! Where's the missus?''
''Don't know!''

327
00:21:58,062 --> 00:21:59,393
Oh, God!

328
00:22:02,867 --> 00:22:06,530
You know what?
Could you forget l told you this?

329
00:22:08,739 --> 00:22:10,263
Well, l kind of have to.

330
00:22:10,541 --> 00:22:12,338
Because the thing is--

331
00:22:12,543 --> 00:22:16,274
The thing is, you know,
that you're married to Emily.

332
00:22:19,049 --> 00:22:21,017
That is what the thing is.

333
00:22:25,456 --> 00:22:26,889
Oh, God.

334
00:22:27,725 --> 00:22:32,059
Things won't be weird between us,
right? Was that stupid?

335
00:22:32,296 --> 00:22:33,627
Me telling you that?

336
00:22:34,198 --> 00:22:36,029
l'm glad you did.

337
00:22:37,801 --> 00:22:39,359
lf nothing else...

338
00:22:39,603 --> 00:22:42,800
...it's always great when someone
tells you they love you.

339
00:22:43,774 --> 00:22:45,264
That's what l said!

340
00:22:47,878 --> 00:22:51,644
-Thank you for being so nice.
-No. Thank you for....

341
00:22:52,950 --> 00:22:54,315
Thank you.

342
00:22:55,019 --> 00:23:00,548
Oh, God. l'm just glad l didn't give you
the cassette l made of all of our songs.

343
00:23:00,724 --> 00:23:03,022
-What songs?
-Oh, you know:

344
00:23:03,193 --> 00:23:05,991
-''With or Without You.''
-Oh, yeah.

345
00:23:06,163 --> 00:23:08,495
-''Everybody Hurts.''
-Oh, yeah.

346
00:23:08,666 --> 00:23:11,260
-''Rhiannon.''
-Why ''Rhiannon''?

347
00:23:11,435 --> 00:23:15,394
Come on, you remember!
ln the living room?

348
00:23:15,873 --> 00:23:18,501
On Monica's laundry?

349
00:23:20,210 --> 00:23:21,905
Not me.

350
00:23:24,281 --> 00:23:25,908
Really.

351
00:23:30,454 --> 00:23:32,149
So, what happened?

352
00:23:32,323 --> 00:23:34,518
Well, it was really hard...

353
00:23:34,692 --> 00:23:37,252
...but l'm glad l did it.

354
00:23:37,428 --> 00:23:39,123
So was l right or wrong?

355
00:23:39,296 --> 00:23:43,699
-Oh, come on, honey, does it really matter?
-No.

356
00:23:43,867 --> 00:23:46,700
Yes. l need it for my score book.

357
00:23:46,870 --> 00:23:48,633
Diary.

358
00:23:50,307 --> 00:23:52,707
-Okay, let's go!
-Yeah, Atlantic City!

359
00:23:52,876 --> 00:23:54,309
Come on!

360
00:23:54,478 --> 00:23:56,469
Atlantic City, baby!

361
00:23:57,781 --> 00:23:59,476
Let's roll some bones.
Hey, Joey!

362
00:23:59,650 --> 00:24:01,277
High-five for rolling bones.

363
00:24:06,724 --> 00:24:08,248
Pheebs, you're leaking.

364
00:24:08,425 --> 00:24:10,416
Oh, my God! Your water broke!

365
00:24:10,627 --> 00:24:12,595
Oh, okay.

366
00:24:13,063 --> 00:24:15,293
Well, don't worry. l call shotgun.

367
00:24:16,767 --> 00:24:19,702
Pheebs, we have to take you
to the hospital now.

368
00:24:19,870 --> 00:24:23,169
Okay. Well, there's probably
one on the way to Atlantic City.

369
00:24:23,340 --> 00:24:26,537
Pheebs, the babies are coming now.

370
00:24:26,710 --> 00:24:29,270
Honey! High-five!
The babies are coming!

371
00:24:31,348 --> 00:24:33,213
Remember when my water broke?

372
00:24:38,022 --> 00:24:40,650
l can't believe Phoebe's going
to have her babies!

373
00:24:40,824 --> 00:24:43,156
l know.
lt's beautiful and amazing.

374
00:24:50,234 --> 00:24:54,364
l can't believe l had to kiss Phoebe
and Rachel every time l left the room.

375
00:24:54,538 --> 00:24:57,769
lt's too bad they didn't
see us having sex.

376
00:24:58,242 --> 00:25:00,403
Do you know anything about women?

377
00:25:02,946 --> 00:25:04,573
-lt's all right.
-Okay.

378
00:25:05,582 --> 00:25:06,571
[ENGLlSH]

